### Nguyen Vuong Quyen

Date of birth Jul 17, 1989

**Gender** Male

Phone

Email

Address Hanoi, Vietnam

Website



#### **OBJECTIVE**

I want to bring my skill and knowledge about research and development software engineering to contribute the development of the company, take the best solutions to valued customers. And thought that I can improve my skill and experience day by day.

#### **EDUCATION**

Aug 2008 - May 2013 Hanoi university of Science and Technology

Major: Software Engineering

GPA: 3.14/4

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

June 2012 - Dec 2012 TriNam Group

Internship

Main responsibilities:

- Develop Web based on Dotnet Nuke open source

+ Main content: develop HR management system

+ Using based (C#)

+ Database: SQL Server

+ Testing the finshed product

Jan 2013 - Jul 2013 Eleisure software

Web developer

Main responsibilities:

- Develop Sale management system

- Using (C#)

- Using Kendo UI, jQuery framework

Jul 2013 - May 2021 Samsung Vietnam Mobile R&D Center

Software Engineer

Main responsibilities:

- Research solutions for some problems in Samsung factory
- Development softwares for Samsung mobile
- Testing and maintain, fix bug

May 2021 - Present

**SDS Vietnam** 

Java Software Engineer Main responsibilities:

- Develop and maintain Lookin Enterprise system

#### **ACTIVITIES**

Jan 2016 - Feb 2017	Cầu Giấy Taewonko club Member of club
Jan 2019 - Apr 2019	Swimming club Member of club

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

2019	TOEIC Certificate with score 640 issued by IIG Vietnam
2016	Software certificate Advanced level issued by SVMC

#### **HONORS & AWARDS**

2013	Samsung Talent Program award

#### **SKILLS**

Language	English, Vietnamese
Computer	Word, Excel, Powerpoint
Programming language	Java
os	Windows, Linux
Database	SQL Server, MySql
Technology	Hibernate, RestFull, MyBatis.
Version control	Git
Enterprise	Java Spring
Clients	Android mobile
Software development processing	Agile
Network	TCP/UDP

#### **INTERESTS**

I like travelling, music, play foot ball...

#### **PROJECTS**

### Sale management

Customer	Singapore customer
Description	The web based system manage the goods in stock and tracing the revenue
Team size	6
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop create and delete product module in store
Technologies used	- Kendo UI, (C#) - jQuery

### SPen SDK

Customer	Samsung mobile
Description	this is the SDK used by many apps in Samsung phones, using the Spen or finger to draw, point on the surface
Team size	30
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop the UI module - Fix bugs - Testing
Technologies used	- Eclipse - Java, C/C++

# SideSync )

Customer	Samsung mobile
Description	An application help sync and control mobile by PC of Tablet
Team size	10
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Develop the Keyboard and Mouse sharing module - Fix bugs - Testing
Technologies used	- Eclipse - Java, C/C++

### TvContentSync

Customer	Samsung Electronics Vietnam
Description	An application help sync and plan schedule to play the programs on TV
Team size	4
My position	Leader
My responsibilities	- Develop main functions - Assign tasks for other members
Technologies used	- Android Studio - Java, Room, RxAndroid, WebSocket

### PlayGalaxy Link

Customer	Samsung mobile
Description	An application for streaming game from PC to Samsung mobile

Team size	5
My position	Leader
My responsibilities	<ul><li>Receive request from customers and analysis them</li><li>Develop main functions</li><li>Assign tasks for other members</li></ul>
Technologies used	- Android Studio - Java, Room, RxAndroid, C/C++ - Git/GitLab

## Galaxy Gift

Customer	SAVINA
Description	An application for give Galaxy users many gift and voucher from many vendors and shops
Team size	2
My position	Leader
My responsibilities	- Develop android client side - Connect to server and get all gift and voucher from server - Testing
Technologies used	- Android Studio - Java, Room, RxAndroid - Git/GitLab

### Samsung Radio FM

Customer	Samsung mobile
Description	An application for listening Radio of Samsung mobile
Team size	13
My position	Sub Leader
My responsibilities	- Develop Scope storaged module - Testing using android espresso - Unit test using JUnit
Technologies used	- Android Studio - Java, Room, RxAndroid, C/C++ - Gerrit

### Lookin Enterprise

Customer	SDS Vietnam
Description	A security assessment system for servers(Windows, Linux)
Team size	3
My position	Leader
My responsibilities	- Develop and maintain rule engine backend
Technologies used	- Inteliji IDEA - Java Spring Boot - Git - Docker